A really great way to get a good back stretch as well as to get a chest opener is with an easy seated pose with a fish pose so Gina and I are just going to come back to back and we are just going to sit in an easy seated pose.
That means your feet are just comfortable and your knees are comfortable and out to the side.
We are going to press our shoulders together.
As we inhale Gina is going to fold forward and just get a nice back stretch and lengthen through her spine and I'm going to open my spine up, opening my heart up to the sky and ready to receive energy.
We're going to inhale, I'm going to lift up and come forward and Gina is going to open her chest now as I release through my spine good.
This feels really good and really nice to come into a rocking back and forth motion.
Inhaling up and exhaling I am going to lean back as Gina stretches through her spine.
Make sure that you talk to your partner so it is not too much weight.
Inhale, are we okay Gina?
Good and exhale come forward or lean back whatever is the case, depending on which side you are on.
Inhaling coming back up and then it is always nice to end your session with a sun moon breath body length so inhale draw the arms up and exhale draw the energy into heart center.